（木こノ葉はの里さとの忍）よーし よし
There you go.
ん？ こんな朝早く どっからだ？
Where'd this one come from
so early in the morning?
な！ こいつは砂隠れ最速の
タカ丸マルじゃないか
Th-This is Takamaru, the fastest
messenger in all the Hidden Sand!
（木ノ葉の里の忍）あ…
Break!
解！
これは…
What's this...?!
第１級の緊急通信文
It's a level-one emergency message!
すぐに暗号班に連絡を
Contact the Cipher Corps
immediately!
（うずまきナルト）
任務に就くのも久しぶりだな
It's sure been a long time
since I've been on a mission...
ワクワクするってばよ
I'm so excited!
（春野はるのサクラ）ナルト
Naruto, accept the mission
without complaint,
どんな任務を言い渡されても
文句を言わずに ちゃんと受けるのよ
no matter what we're ordered to do.
（ナルト）ああ
分かってるってばよ
I know!
（はたけカカシ）だと いいけど
I hope so...
（くノ一）どいた どいた！
（ナルト･サクラ）うわあ
Move it, move it!
（サクラ）何？
What was that?
Watch it, you! Be more careful!
危ねえじゃねえか
気をつけろってばよ
（カカシ）暗号班が呼び出されたか
So the Cipher Corps
was summoned, huh...?
すると さっきの鳥が
運んできたのは…
Then what the bird from earlier
brought must've been...
You said there's
a level-one emergency message?
（くノ一）
第１級の緊急通信文だと？
Are you sure?
間違いないのか
（木ノ葉の里の忍）はい ここに
Yes. It's right here...
（くノ一）砂からか…
It's from the Sand, huh...?
解！
Break!
（木ノ葉の里の忍）
そいつが きたってことは
That message coming here means...
（木ノ葉の里の忍）
砂に 何かあったに違いない
No doubt something's happened
in the Sand!
（くノ一）分かった
すぐに解読する
Okay!
I'll get right to deciphering it!
♪～
A voice heard in the distance gives me a hint.
tooku de kikoeru koe wo hinto ni
One by one like-minded people are standing up.
hitori mata hitori tachiagaru doushi
Lets overturn all the everyday, monotonous things.
kurikaesu dake no fudan doori kutsugaesu
I'm ready, are you ready?
junbi iize are you ready
A shiver spreads through my body, violently ringing stomping.
karadajuu furuwasu shindou ni hageshiku uchinarase yo stomping
Constantly stirring in me, it calls me.
taezu tsuki ugokasu call me
Catching that unchanging, never wavering story, Come on!
kawarazu yuru ga nutsukamu story come on
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Are you ready for a few risks?
hey yo whoa tashou no risuku wa kakugo desho
You have to get up no matter how many times you fall. (Get it on!)
nanka korundatte tatsu get it on
It's not some conspiracy, just a paper-thin session
nare ai ja nai ze kami hitoe no sesshon
The pent up feelings turn into a crystal.
irikunda kanjou kidzukiageta kesshou
The rising cheers will become your courage.
wakiagaru kansei ga yuuki tonaru
So stand up now, no matter how much pain you feel.
tachiagareba ima ijou kurushimi tomonau
But in the end I'm sure you'll laugh.
soredemo saigo wa kitto warau
Everything will be swept away in victory and cheer.
subete sarau shouri to kansei
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
～♪
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Team Kakashi
Deployed
（カンクロウ）
烏からすのスピードに
Who'd have thought you could keep up
with Crow's speed...
ついてこられる とはなあ
（サソリ）ハエが
止まりそうだったぜ
It looked like the fly was
about to land, you see.
（カンクロウ）くっ…
（デイダラ）思い出した うん
I remember now.
この人柱力じんちゅうりきには
何人かの兄弟がいたな
This Jinchuriki guy had some siblings.
その中に傀儡くぐつを使うヤツが
いるって聞いた
And I heard that one of them
uses Puppets...
たぶん こいつがそうだな うん
This is probably that guy...
名前は確か カンタロウ
いや カンパチだったか？
I think his name was Kantaro...
I mean, Kanpachi, or something...?
（カンクロウ）カンクロウだ
It's Kankuro!
くっ…
（サソリ）お前の相手は
俺だって言ってるだろうが
I'm telling you I'm your opponent.
お前も見てねえで
さっさと行け 邪魔だ
And you quit gawking
and get out of here.
You're in the way.
（デイダラ）そうだな
そうさせてもらう うん
You're right... I'll be going, then.
おい 待て！
Hey, hold it!
Don't make me repeat myself...
（サソリ）何度も言わせるな
お前の相手は俺だ
I'm your opponent...
（カンクロウ）
チッ さっさと こいつを片づけて
追いかけるしかないじゃん
It looks like I'll have to take care
of this guy
and then go after the other one...
（デイダラ）運がないな
You're sure unlucky...
サソリの旦那は恐らく お前にとって
最悪の相手だ うん
My man Sasori just might be
the worst possible opponent for you.
（バキ）まだ トラップが
残っているかもしれん
There might still be
some traps remaining...
（バキ）慎重にな
Be careful...
（砂すなの里さとの忍）追跡部隊
出動準備 完了しました
Preparations for mobilization of
the tracking unit have been completed.
（バキ）よし すぐに
カンクロウを追いかけろ
All right, go after Kankuro immediately.
敵を見つけても
極力 戦闘は避けるんだぞ
Even if you find the enemy,
avoid battle as best you can.
あくまでも目的は
敵のアジトの発見だ
Our only goal is to find
the enemy hideout.
（砂の里の忍たち）はっ
- Yes, sir!
- Yes,sir!
アジトを発見次第
すぐに風影かぜかげ様 奪還チームを出す
We'll send out the Kazekage rescue team
as soon as we find their hideout.
必ず情報を持ち帰ってこい ゆけ！
You'd better come back
with some information!
Get going!
（砂の里の忍たち）はっ
- Yes, sir!
（バキ）カンクロウ…
くれぐれも ムチャはするなよ
Kankuro... Make sure you don't do
anything reckless...
見せてやろうじゃん！
俺の カラクリ演劇を
I'll show you my Puppet Show!
There! There!
ほらほら！
やるじゃん けど…
You're pretty good...
However...
途中から黒蟻くろありが消えたのは
気付かなかっただろ
You didn't notice that
the Black Ant was gone, did you?
いくぜ
Here goes!
からくり演劇
Puppet Show!
黒秘技 危機一髪
Puppet Show
Secret Black Move Iron Maiden!
終劇
The show's over.
（ナルト）はあ？ 金塊輸送の護衛
Whaaat?!
A guard for gold bullion
transport convoy?!
（綱手つなで）ああん！
なんか文句あんのか こら
Huh? You got a problem?!
思いっきりＣランクじゃん
That's totally a C-rank mission!
そんな任務
ノーサンキューだってばよ
I'll just have to say no thanks
to a mission like that...
（サクラ）文句 言わないって
言ったばかりなのに…
And here I just told him
not to complain.
（カカシ）あんまりワガママ
言わないでちょうだいよ
Please don't act so selfish...
怒られんの俺なんだから
I'm the one she's going to get mad at...
（綱手）やっぱり こういう
リアクションか やれやれ
I knew he'd react like this...
Good grief...
（シズネ）アハハハッ
やっぱりですね アハハハッ…
Ohh, just as you thought...
（うみのイルカ）
はあ ナルト お前 精神的には
全然 成長してないのな
Naruto, you haven't matured
mentally at all, have you...?
（綱手）ナルト 一応 お前の
復帰戦ということを考えて
Naruto...
I gave you an easier mission since
this is more or less a comeback for you...
軽めの任務に しておいたんだが
よけいな お世話だってばよ
I didn't ask for this!
I-I'm sorry, Master! I'll give him
a good scolding later...
すいません 師匠
あとで私がよく言っておきますから
（サクラ）
このバカ あんた師匠の恐ろしさを
知らないから そんな口が…
Y-You moron!
You can talk like that
because you don't know know
frightening she can be... Shannaro!
しゃーんなろー！
（綱手）任務の詳細は
ここに書いてある
The details of the mission
are written here.
（カカシ）はい
Right!
（ナルト）
ったく ３代目のじいちゃんは
もっと物分かりがよかったってばよ
Geez, man...
Grandpa Third was much
more understanding...
ああん なんか言ったか！
Huh? Did you say something?!
（サクラ）
だから いいかげんにしろ！
Hey! Knock it off!
大変です ５代目！
Th-There's trouble... Fifth!
（綱手）なんだ 騒々しい
What's all the commotion...?
（くノ一）
先ほど砂から緊急通信が…
We just received an emergency message
from the Sand...
（ナルト）あ… 砂？
The Sand...?!
（綱手）緊急通信だと？
Did you say an emergency message?!
（くノ一）解読したものです
This is what we have deciphered...
何！
What?!
砂！
Sand?!
A clone...?
砂分身だと
Oh... my god...
（イルカ）こ… これは！
It can't be...
（シズネ）そんな！
Hey... What happened...?
（ナルト）なあ 何が
あったんだってばよ？
The Kazekage of the Hidden Sand
has been taken
砂隠れの風影が 暁あかつきという
組織の者に連れ去られた
by members of the organization
called the Akatsuki.
（カカシ）ああ
（サクラ）あっ
あ… 我愛羅があらが
Gaara...
Those guys again, huh...?
また あいつらか
We have more information
concerning the Akatsuki.
（綱手）
暁に関しては我々のほうが
多くの情報を持っている
And so the Hidden Sand has
officially requested our help...
そこで砂隠れから
正式に応援を要請してきた
（シズネ）ああ！ 綱手様
まさか カカシ班を…
Tsunade-sama, don't tell me
you're going to have Team Kakashi...?!
This is a time of emergency.
緊急時だ のんびり
人選している暇はない
I can't be wasting time
on personnel selection.
それに 実際に暁と戦った者もいる
And besides, we've got someone here
who's actually fought against
the Akatsuki...
（シズネ）それは そうですが…
I understand that, but...
I will now issue Team Kakashi
a new mission.
（綱手）これよりカカシ班に
改めて任務を言い渡す
Go to the Village Hidden
in the Sand immediately,
直ちに砂隠れの里へ行き
状況を把握し木ノ葉へ伝達
find out what's going on and
report back to the Leaf...
After that, you will follow the orders
of the Hidden Sand
その後 砂隠れの命に従い
彼らをバックアップしろ
and provide them with back-up!
（カンクロウ）うう… なぜだ？
How...?
How...?!
なぜなんだ？
How can he read
my movements like this...?
なぜ こうまで こちらの
動きが読まれるんだ
しかも ヤツは さっきから
ほとんど動いてねえ
And on top of that,
he's hardly moved at all the whole time...
What's the matter?
Are you already finished...?
（サソリ）
どうした もう終わりか？
（カンクロウ）くっ…
Like hell I am!
んなわけねえじゃん！
Poisoned Mist Inferno...
毒霧地獄 バリバリ100連発！
Consecutive Needle Combo!
（カンクロウ）ウッ…
（サソリ）終わりか？
Are you finished?
No way... How is he not affected by
being in the Poisoned Mist?!
（カンクロウ）
バカな！ 毒霧の中に
いたってのに平気なのかよ
Making people wait any longer than this
goes against my policy...
（サソリ）
これ以上 人を待たせるのは
俺のポリシーに反するんでな
そろそろ こちらから
いかせてもらうぜ
I think it's just about my turn now!
Salamander has an iron wall defense...
山椒魚さんしょううおは鉄壁の防御
数万トンの岩の直撃にも
耐えることができる
It can withstand a direct hit from
a few thousand tons of rocks...
フフフッ
You won't be able to inflict even
a scratch on me.
お前は俺に 傷１つ
つけることもできねえ
It's safe to say the defensive strength
of that puppet
（サソリ）
確かに その傀儡くぐつの防御能力は
最高レベルと言っていいだろう
is indeed of the highest level.
However...
だが 弱点が ないわけじゃない
There's always a weakness.
It's futile!
（カンクロウ）ムダだ！
あ！
N-No way...
バ… バカな
He figured out Salamander's weakness
in one glance...?
山椒魚さんしょううおの弱点を
ひと目で見破っただと？
う… うわ！
うう…
No matter how strong the puppet may be,
（サソリ）例え
どんな頑丈な傀儡くぐつでも
the movable parts of the joints
are weaker than the other parts.
稼働部分である関節は
ほかより強度が劣るものだ
Now then, shall we go for the finale?
さて フィナーレといくか
（湯飲みにヒビが入った音）
（テマリ）ん…
I usually don't believe
in stuff like this, but...
（テマリ）こういうのは
あまり信じないんだが
I've kind of got
a bad feeling about this...
なんだか胸騒ぎがする
（カンクロウ）てやあ！
How...?
（カンクロウ）
なぜだ？ なぜ こうまで
仕込みの手順を読まれるんだ
How can he read
my hidden weapon attack schemes...?
（サソリ）筋はいい
だが 相手が悪かったな
You've got solid talent...
However, you picked
the wrong opponent.
Your puppets
with the hidden poison weapons...
お前の傀儡くぐつ
毒仕込みのカラクリは
全て お見通しだ
I can see through them all...
（カンクロウ）
ああ 烏からす 黒蟻くろあり 山椒魚さんしょううお！
Crow! Black Ant! Salamander!
This is the first time
（カンクロウ）ここまで仕込みを
読まれたのは初めてだ
my hidden weapon attacks
have been read like this...
（サソリ）フフッ
不思議そうな顔してる
You look puzzled...
You're wondering how
I figured out your attacks, huh?
なぜ仕込みがバレた？
そりゃあ そうだ
Of course I did.
Crow...
烏からす 黒蟻くろあり 山椒魚さんしょううお
Black Ant...
Salamander...
The one who created these
three puppets is none other... than me!
この３体の傀儡くぐつ人形を
作ったのは ほかでもない
この俺だ！
（カンクロウ）な！
（カエル）ゲロゲロ ゲロゲロ
（カエル）ゲーロゲロ ゲーロゲロ
（カエル）ゲロゲロ
（自来也じらいや）うわ！
（自来也）ええ… ろ…？
（カエル）ゲコ
その巻物は…
That scroll...?!
You idiot! Hurry up and show it to me!
バカもん！ 早く見せろ
（カエル）ゲコ
（自来也）ん～ 何々？
砂隠れの里の風影が…
What...?
The Kazekage of the Hidden Sand
has been...
Looks like this isn't the time
to be sleeping like this!
こりゃ のんびり寝ている
場合じゃないのう
（サソリ）少々 人を待たせる
ことになってしまったが
I ended up making
someone wait a bit...
But I never thought my opponent
would be
お下がりを持っている
カワイイ後輩が相手とは
one of my adorable juniors
using hand-me-downs.
久々に楽しい戦いだったぞ
I haven't had such a fun fight
in quite some time.
Then, you're... the celebrated master
craftsman of the puppet unit,
じゃあ てめえが傀儡くぐつ部隊の
天才造形師とうたわれた
Sasori of the Red Sand?!
赤砂のサソリだってのか？
I'm honored that a kid like you
knows my name.
（サソリ）お前のようなガキにまで
名を知られているとは 光栄だな
You left the Sand over twenty years ago.
20年以上も前に
砂を抜けたお前が なぜ…
What're you doing here?!
（サソリ）死ぬ前に
そんなに聞いてどうする？
What's the point of asking such
a thing before you die?
あ… うあ
くっ… あ…
体が しびれてきやがった
My body's getting numb...
Don't tell me he also uses poison...
まさか こいつも毒を…
But when?
だが いつ？
I know! At that moment!
そうか あのとき！
The poison's circulating, huh...?
You're finished!
（サソリ）
毒が回ってきたな とどめだ
ん？
ふん
苦しむだけだというのに
そうまでして生きていたいなら
You're just going to suffer.
But if you want to live that badly...
I won't finish you off!
とどめは やめだ
However, that poison will kill you
in less than three days.
ただ その毒だ
３日ともたずに お前は死ぬ
Gaara...
（カンクロウ）我愛羅…
ちっきしょう
Damn it...!
There he is! He's over there!
（砂の里の忍）いたぞ あそこだ
倒れてる
He's collapsed!
And his puppets are smashed...
（砂の里の忍）傀儡くぐつもバラバラだぞ
Okay, we're off now!
（ナルト）んじゃ
行ってくるってばよ
We'll be back, Master.
では綱手師匠 行って参ります
Right...
（綱手）ああ
（イルカ）ん…
Naruto, good luck!
ナルト 頑張れよ
Thanks.
おう
Hey!
おお これから任務か ナルト？
Are you off on a mission now, Naruto?
That's right!
（ナルト）押忍
Oh, more importantly.
（自来也）おっと それより
綱手 情報だ
Tsunade, I've got some information
for you.
砂隠れの風影が…
- The Kazekage of the Hidden Sand...
- I know.
（綱手）知ってる 今から
こいつらを砂に送るところだ
I'm just about to send them off
to the Sand now.
Right, right.
うん うん
You know about the Akatsuki
and Naruto, don't you...?
（自来也）暁とナルトのことは
お前も知っとるだろうのォ
緊急事態だからな
最善の選択をしたまでだ
It's an emergency situation you see...
I just made the best choice I could.
Oh, come on...
まったく お前は…
Naruto, come here for a second.
ナルト ちょっと こっちこい
Hm?
（ナルト）ん？
いいか ナルト
暁 相手に決して無理はするな
Listen up, Naruto.
Don't get reckless against the Akatsuki.
They've got business with me.
あいつら俺に用があるんだから
So this time I'll go to them!
今度こそ こっちから
出向いてやらあ
You have indeed gotten stronger...
確かにお前は強くなったがのォ
But if you don't keep cool,
you'll just be asking for trouble.
冷静を欠けば 必ず
墓穴を掘ることになるぞ
すぐに熱くなるのは
お前の悪い癖だのォ
Losing your cool right away
is a bad habit of yours.
Naruto... I think you know...
ナルト 分かってるとは思うが
あの力は使うなよ
But don't use that power.
I know...
（ナルト）分かってるってばよ
Kakashi...
カカシ ナルトがあまり
ムチャしないよう見張ってくれ
Keep an eye on Naruto and make sure
he doesn't do anything too reckless.
I'm counting on you. Okay?
頼んだぞ のォ
Okay.
（カカシ）はい
Kakashi-sensei, Sakura-chan,
let's get a move on!
（ナルト）カカシ先生
サクラちゃん
さっさと行くってばよ
H-Hey, wait up!
（サクラ）
ああ… ちょっと待ってよ
We're off.
（カカシ）では
Oh boy...
ったく のォ
Are you worried?
心配か？
No, I'm not...
いえ あいつは もう
私の心配するような
He's no longer a weak Shinobi
I need to worry about...
弱い忍びでは ありませんから
And the same goes for Sakura.
それにサクラも…
Growth is sure a mysterious thing.
（綱手）成長とは
不思議なもんだなあ
Hang on, Gaara!
（ナルト）待ってろよ 我愛羅
When I look up at the sky.
sora wo miagereba
♪～
The stars, see, are sparkling.
hoshitachi ga hora matataiteru
Each giving off its own light.
kono hoshi no hitotachi mitai ni
Like the people on this planet.
samazama na hikari wo hanatte
Yeah, so among them, I too,
sono naka de boku mo
want to shine particularly bright.
hitokiwa kagayaite itain da
I close my eyes and make a vow in my heart,
me wo tojite kokoro ni chikau
and entrust my dreams to that shooting star.
nagareboshi ni yume wo takushite
I'm in my usual park.
koko wa itsumo no kouen
I can see the night scenery on the slide.
yakei ga mieru suberidai no ue
That's been my special seat for years.
mukashi kara boku no tokutouseki
Whenever I'm worried about something, I come here.
nayami ga areba koko ni kurun desu
Just like then, I'm on my way to my dreams.
ano koro no mama yume no tochuu de
But unable to fulfil them.
ima de kanaerarezu ni irun desu
Maybe this is the end of the line.
moshikashite koko ga mou shuuten
There are days when I say weak things like that.
nante yowane wo haite shimaisou na hi mo aru
But every time, I remember.
demo sono tabi ni omoidasu
That starry sky where I looked for a shooting star.
nagareboshi wo sagashite ano hoshizora
The wish I made when I was little hasn't changed even now.
chiisana koro no negaigoto ima mukashi mo kawaranai mama
When I look up at the sky.
sora wo miagereba
The stars, see, are sparkling.
hoshitachi ga hora matataiteru
Each giving off its own light.
kono hoshi no hitotachi mitai ni
Like the people on this planet.
samazama na hikari wo hanatte
Yeah, so among them, I too,
sono naka de boku mo
want to shine particularly bright.
hitokiwa kagayaite itain da
I close my eyes and make a vow in my heart,
me wo tojite kokoro ni chikau
～♪
and entrust my dreams to that shooting star.
nagareboshi ni yume wo takushite
Next Episode
What's the matter, Kankuro?
ん どうしたカンクロウ？
Actually, my makeup remover
doesn't really agree with my skin.
実はメイク落としが合わなくてよ
At a time like that, you need
this makeup remover gauze.
そんなときは
このメイク拭き取りガーゼ
It's gentle on the skin as
the microfibers help remove the dirt
ミクロの繊維が毛穴の奥の
汚れまで かき出すから
肌に優しくメイクオフだ
from inside your pores.
おお 隈取くまどり 落ちる落ちる
Ooh, the Kumadori is coming right off.
And not only that, if you buy now,
おまけに今 購入すると
同じ物がもう１つに
you'll get one more for free along
with a handy storage case.
持ち運び便利な
専用収納ケースまで付いてくるんだ
Whoa, this is serious.
I'd better hurry right to the Sand shop.
そりゃ大変だ
すぐ 砂の売店まで
急ぐっきゃねえじゃん
Next time: "The Jinchuriki's Tears"
The Jinchuriki's Tears
次回「人柱力じんちゅうりきの涙」
I
n
t
e
l
i
g
e
n
c
e
R
p
o
r
t
b
y
t
h
e
A
n
b
u
B
l
a
c
k
O
p
s
Intelligence Research Report by
the Anbu Black Ops.
The Leaf and Sand Alliance.
（綱手）中忍(ちゅうにん)試験のさなか
始まった木ノ葉崩し
The attempt to crush the Leaf began
suddenly during the Chunin Exams.
The Sand Shinobi betrayed the Leaf by conspiring
with Orochimaru in an attack against them.
木ノ葉を裏切り
大蛇丸おろちまるに加担した砂の襲撃を受け
And the Leaf was hit extremely hard by such
events as the death of the Third Hokage.
３代目 火影ほかげが絶命
木ノ葉の受けた被害は甚大であった
後に風影は大蛇丸に
暗殺されていたことが判明
However, it became known that the Kazekage had
already been assassinated by Orochimaru.
砂隠れの里は 事件の発端が
大蛇丸によるものと公表し
As soon as the Village Hidden
in the Sand learned of this,
they made public that Orochimaru
was the culprit behind the incident
and announced a full surrender.
全面的な降伏を宣言
As the recovery of national power
was urgently needed,
国力の復旧を急務としていた
木ノ葉は砂との同名を締結した
the Leaf accepted their surrender and
the Leaf and the Sand formed an alliance.
Presently, the Sand is incorporating
the Leaf's training program
現在では新人育成に
木ノ葉の演習プログラムを
取り入れるなど 交流も深い
in their development of recruits
and interaction between Leaf
and Sand Shinobi is on the rise.
ちなみに シカマルと
テマリの交際疑惑だが
Incidentally, as for the alleged relationship
between Shikamaru and Temari,
Shikamaru himself
commented by saying
シカマル当人が中忍ちゅうにん試験の
打ち合わせとコメント
that they were just having a meeting
about the Chunin Exams.
It seems Naruto jumped to
the wrong conclusion.
ナルトの早とちりだった模様
From here on, it is likely that the Leaf and the Sand
will continue to forge an amicable alliance.
以上 今後も木ノ葉と砂は
良好な同盟関係を
築いていくと思われる
T
o
b
e
c
o
n
t
i
n
u
e
d
.